NYSUT Division of Research and Educational Services, Maria Neira Files. 6174/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Education and Learning Trust Progress, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  4/22/08. Presentation bullet points
- ELT Meeting, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  02/08/08 at 1:30PM in Maria's Office. Scenarios; memos
- ELT Promotional Video, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  01/30/08 at 10:30AM in Exec. Conf. Rm 1. Video script
- Capital District TC - NBCT, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  11/5/07 at 4PM in Maria's Office. Memo re teacher leadership; handwritten notes
- ELT Regional Report, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  Sept. 2007. Regional reports from western NY, Hudson Valley, Nassau, Suffolk, Southern Tier, Capital District/northern NY; Utica/Rome, Syracuse
- ELT Meeting, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  02/15/07 at 3PM in Conf. Rm. 3. Agenda; memo re brochure mailing
- Interim Report on the Trust Self Study, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  Professional development needs assessment survey; memo re interim report on the ELT self study; bullet points from meeting with regional staff in Cooperstown
- Executive Committee, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  11/17/09 at 1PM. Officers reports; NYSUT Dual Credit Task Force Final Report; letter from Maria Neira to Education Commissioner David Steiner re Race to the Top grant application, November 2, 2009; State Education Department discussion item, Transforming Teaching and Ensuring an Equitable Distribution of Qualified Teachers in NYS, November 10
- NYSUT Exec Committee Ballot, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  Ballot by Maria Neira supporting NYSUT endorsement of Kathy Hochul (D) in special election in 26th Congressional District
- Executive Committee Meeting, Maria Neira, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  November 17, 2009. Agenda; minutes of Executive Committee meeting of October 22; officers reports; NYSUT Dual Credit Task Force Final Report
- NYSUT Exec. Committee Meeting: Web-cam from Elmhurst, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  10/22/09 at 2PM. Report of NYSUT vice president Maria Neira to the Executive Committee; NYSUT testimony to the Assembly Standing Committee on Ways and Means on the Estimated Budget Deficit for the 2009-2010 state fiscal year, October 21, 2009; research brief, National Education Association Visiting Scholars Series, "A Time of Peril for Education," Diane Ravitch, New York University
- NYSUT Executive Committee, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  10/05/09 at 4:15PM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Memo re recommendation to endorse moderate Dede Scozzafava (R) in special election in the 23rd Congressional District
- Executive Committee Meeting, Maria Neira, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  September 25, 2009. NYSUT Building Corporation Board of Directors meeting agenda; Conflict of Interest Policy for NYSUT Officials and Employees; draft NYSUT redistricting plan
- Executive Committee, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  09/25/09 at 1PM. Agenda; Board of Directors meeting agenda; minutes of Board of Directors meeting of July 23; NYSUT Building Corporation membership meeting agenda, September 25; report of vice president Maria Neira; newspaper clippings; NYSUT redistricting plan; memo re PSC/UUP concerns; New York Teacher story list
- Executive Committee, Maria Neira, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  7/23/09. Agenda; Member Benefits Trust 403(b) Endorsement Survey summary and results; memo re proposed building purchase; NYSUT Building Corporation Board of Directors meeting agenda, July 23
- Executive Committee, Maria Neira, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  6/4/09. Agenda; minutes of Executive Committee meeting of May 12; officers' reports; NYSUT and NYSUT Building Corporation financial statements as of April 30, 2009; requests for affiliation
- Executive Committee, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  6/4/09 at 1:00PM. Agenda; report of vice president Maria Neira; NYSUT 2009-2010 Budget for Executive Committee, June 4, 2009
- NYSUT Exec. Committee, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  05/12/09 at 12 Noon in Desmond. Agenda; officers' reports; NYSUT member benefits report; preliminary analysis of President Obama's FY 2010 budget proposal; document, "Race to the Top: Promising State Models"
- Exec. Committee, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  03/24/09 at 8:30AM in Desmond Hotel, Fort Orange Room. Agenda; report of vice president Maria Neira
- Executive Committee Meeting, Maria Neira, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  3/24/09. Agenda; 2009 Proposed Constitutional and Bylaw Amendments (for 37th Representative Assembly); requests for affiliation; memo to the Business and Labor Coalition of New York from the Gotham Research Group re the Fair Share Tax Concept: An Overview of Survey Findings, March 23
- Executive Committee, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  2/27/09 at 1:00PM. Oral report of vice president Maria Neira
- Executive Committee, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  1/15/09 at 2:00PM. Agenda; officers' reports; financial statements; requests for affiliation
- Executive Committee, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  12/12/08 at 1:00PM. Minutes; dues proposal; memo re CUNY master plan 2004-2008; briefing re differentiated accountability and growth models; report of vice president Maria Neira; statement for Maria Neira re status of Sandy Feldman Award and grant applications, noting lack of candidates
- Executive Committee Meeting, Maria Neira, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  11/18/08. Report of the Executive Director to the Executive Committee; requests for affiliation
- NYSUT Executive Committee, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  11/18/08 at 2PM Webcast. Agenda; minutes of October 24 meeting; report of vice president Maria Neira
- Executive Committee, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  9/26/08 at 4PM Conference Call. Facilitative memo
- Executive Committee, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  9/11/08 at 1:00PM. Agenda; resolution establishing NYSUT Nonqualified Employees' Retirement Plan (managerial/confidential); Representative Assembly proposed deadlines; reports of officers
- Executive Committee, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  8/13/08 at 1:00PM. NYSUT position papers re virtual learning, improving access and support for students with disabilities in technical education, and improving the state's assessment system; report of vice president Maria Neira
- Executive Committee, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  6/5/08 at 1PM in Conf. Rm. B&C. Agenda; minutes of meeting of May 13; NYSUT 2008-09 Budget, prepared by Office of Secretary-Treasurer for Executive Committee meeting; legislative update; officers' reports; financial statements
- Executive Committee, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  05/13/08 at 3PM Webcast. Agenda; officers' reports; report of general counsel
- RA Set Design, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  12/09/09 at 3PM. Seating plan for Representative Assembly
- RA Theme Meeting: Immediately Following the NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  08/31/09. Revised list of 2010 RA proposed themes
- RA Speech Practice, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  03/18/09 at 3:30PM in NYSUT Auditorium. Fifth draft of prepared remarks for Maria Neira at Representative Assembly
- Maria's RA Speech/Background Materials, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  Prepared remarks for NYSUT 37th Annual Representative Assembly, sixth draft
- RA Speech, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  2/17/09 Conf. Call. Report by Center for American Progress, "From Qualifications to Results: Promoting Teacher Effectiveness through Federal Policy," January 2009; report by Economic Policy Institute, "Education Accountability Policy in the New Administration"; first draft of remarks of vice president Maria Neira to 37th NYSUT Representative Assembly, February 9, 2009
- RA Video Meeting, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  01/07/09 at 4:30PM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 1. Agreement with Gracey Communications Group, Inc., for video production services for Representative Assembly 2009
- RA Reporter, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  Daily newsletter from Representative Assembly though April 4, 2009
- Widmeyer Conf. Call, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  01/28/09 at 3:30PM in Maria's Office. Maria Neira's RA speech outline and commentary on draft from Neira
- RA Report, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  April 7-13, 2008. Schedule of events; list of invitees (guest speakers); media summary with newspaper clippings of coverage
- RA Staff Meeting, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  03/19/08 at 2PM in NYSUT Auditorium. Program; facilitative memos
- Gracey Video Meeting, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  12/11/07 at 1PM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 1. Facilitative memo
- RA Program Planning, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  9/21/07 at 12:00PM in Dick's Office. Tentative program; tentative schedule for pre-RA local leaders and Retire Council conference
- RA Speech Meeting and Teach New York/Vouchers Meeting, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  02/1/06 at 2-4PM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 1 and 4-5pm in Exec. Conf. Rm. 1. Facilitative memo
- RA Site Visit, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  10/06/06 at 11-3PM in Washington DC. Memo re agenda
- NYSUT RA, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  RA Reporter daily proceedings, noting unification of NYSUT and NEA/NY, endorsement of Hillary Clinton for re-election to U.S. Senate; list of Community Service Awards nominees; program and agenda for pre-RA local and retiree council presidents conference
- RA, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  2008 NYSUT Representative Assembly "Convention Call" and pre-NYSUT RA Local & Retiree Council Presidents Conference
- NYSUT RA 2008 Representative Assembly (Box 5, Folder 1)
  April 10-12, 2008. Tabbed scripts for general sessions for Maria Neira
- NYSUT 35th Annual Representative Assembly [folder 1 of 2], 2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  04/26-28/07, 2007 Black Book. Agenda and tabbed script for RA general sessions 1-2; report of the Resolutions Committee, session 1
- NYSUT 35th Annual Representative Assembly [folder 2 of 2], 2007 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  04/26-28/07, 2007 Black Book. Tabbed script for RA general sessions 3-5
- GLSEN: RA in DC, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Gay, Lesbian and Straight Education Network internship job description
- RA, Rochester: GLSEN, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  RA Reporter daily proceeding newsletters; brochure, "Dealing with Legal Matters Surrounding Students' Sexual Orientation and Gender Identity"; brochure, "What can you do about anti-LGBT bias in America's k-12 schools?"; materials re table assignment for GLSEN at Representative Assembly; list of chapters; GLSEN newsletter, Respect, September 2006
- NY Teacher: Going Forward, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  12/01/09 at 4PM in Dick's Office. Memo confirming meeting to discuss the future of New York Teacher newsletter
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  11/09/09 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Story list for November 26 issue
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  10/26/09 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Story list for November 12 issue
- New NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  10/26/09 at 1PM in Dick's Office. List of possible new titles for New York Teacher; design timeline
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  10/13/09 at 11AM in Conf. Rm. 2. Story list for October 29 issue
- NY Teacher, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  9/14/09 at 11AM in Executive Conference Room 2. Story list for October 1 issue
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  6/01/09 at 1PM in NYC. Articles from New York Times re Newsweek downsizing to fit smaller audience
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  06/01/09. Story list for June 18 issue
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  5/18/09 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Story list for June 4 issue
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  4/20/09 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Story list for May 7 issue
- New York Teacher Revisioning and Future Planning, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  03/25/09 at 3:30PM in Dick's Office. Document re rationale for revising New York Teacher; timeline for revisioning
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  3/2/09 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Story list for March 19 issue
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  2/17/09 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Issue of January 22, 2009, New York Teacher; story list for March 5 issue
- NY Teacher, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  01/16/09 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 1. Story list for February 5 issue
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  1/5/09 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Story list for January 22 issue; memo re poll questions on school issues; handwritten letter to Maria Neira from teacher, thanking her for posters of the late Robert F. Kennedy; letter to the editor of Albany Times Union from Albany Public School Teachers' Association president re school aid formula
- NY Teacher Planning Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  12/01/08 at 4PM in Dick's Office. Editorial planning calendar for several months; memo re meeting
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  11/17/08 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Story list for December 11 issue
- NY Teacher, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  10/06/08 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Story list for October 23 issue
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  9/22/08 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Story list for October 9 issue
- NY Teacher Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  9/8/08 at 11AM in Exec. Conf. Rm. 2. Story list for September 25 issue; press release, "Governor Patterson Announces Hearings Statewide on Property Tax Relief"
- Communications, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  6/13/08 at 4PM in Maria's Office. Memo re meeting with Maria Neira
- New York Teacher Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  5/19/08 at 11AM in Exec. Conference Rm. 2. Story list for June 5 issue
- NY Teacher Redesign Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  04/16/09 at 2PM in Dick's Office. Communications Department two-year savings and reinvestment plan; justification for revisioning (downsizing) New York Teacher; timeline; 2009-2010 issues and deadlines
- New York Teacher Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  3/10/08 at 11AM in Exec. Conference Rm. 2. Story list for March 27
- New York Teacher Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  2/25/08 at 11AM in Exec. Conference Rm. 2. Story list for March 13; NYSUT at-large directors Regents represented; 2008 Contract for Excellence Summary and Survey, Newburgh Enlarged City School District
- New York Teacher Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  1/28/08 at 11AM in Exec. Conference Rm. 2. Story list for February 14
- New York Teacher Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  1/14/08 at 11AM in Exec. Conference Rm. 2. Story list for January 31
- New York Teacher Stories, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  Printouts of articles from various issues
- Officers' Advisory Committee, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  09/21/09 at 1PM in Conf. Rm. B&C. Agenda; internal summary of NYSUT's Position on Charter Schools; NYSUT Action Steps; profiles of approved charter schools; NYSUT affiliated charter schools; Race to the Top Update; related memos
- Officers' Advisory Committee, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  05/19/09 at 12:30PM in Conf. Rm. B&C. Agenda
- Officers' Advisory Committee, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  01/08/09 at 1PM in Conf. Rm. B7C. Agenda; NYSUT 2009-1020 Budget Advocacy, outlining talking points re state budget; list of NYSUT compensation expenses; press release, "Governor Patterson Presents Economic Recovery Agenda to President-Elect Obama," December 29, 2008
- Officers' Advisory Committee, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  05/07/08 at 2PM in Conf. Rm. B&C. Agenda; Local and Retiree Council Presidents post-conference survey summary and results
- Officers' Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  12/8/09 at 9:30AM. Discussion paper for Board of Regents re Transforming Teaching and Ensuring an Equitable Distribution of Qualified Teachers in New York State, November 10, 2009; description of framework and objectives of the New York Opportunity to Learn Summit 2010; related memos
- Officers' Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  12/02/09 at 9:30AM. Agenda for Officers' meeting; agenda for Cabinet meeting; financial statements; document, "Renaming New York Teacher: Summary and Survey Results," December 2009
- Officers' Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  10/20/09 at 10AM in Dick's Office. Agenda; confidential outline of Regents/State Education Department proposal for Race to the Top
- Officers' Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  10/14/08 at 11:30AM in Conf. Rm. D. Agenda; draft letter to Chancellor Robert Bennett from NYSUT vice president Maria Neira, urging Regents to seek significant increases in state aid to schools
- Officers' Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  10/02/08 at 4PM in Dick's Office. Agenda; NYSUT Policy Prohibiting Harassment; 2009 Segal Health Plan Cost Trend Survey
- Officers' Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  9/9/09 at 9:30AM. Memos
- Officers' Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  6/17/09 at 11:00AM. Agenda; NYSUT Harassment-Free Workplace Policy (adding predisposing genetic characteristics and gender identity or expression); memo re local presidents election results; letter from NYSUT president Dick Ianuzzi to president of Professional Staff Congress (NYSUT's staff union) re relationship, noting "insurmountable" differences, June 16
- Officers, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  5/20/09 at 9:30AM. Solicitation guidelines
- Officers, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  05/06/09 at 11AM in Dick's Office. Discussion topics for meeting with the Commissioner; proposal for charitable contribution administration from the secretary-treasurer, noting consistent spending over budget, April 15
- Officers' Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  04/15/09 at 10AM in Dick's Office. Agenda; agenda for Cabinet meeting; financial statements; draft program for NYSUT Local Action Project; draft program for NYSUT New Local Presidents Conference; memo re NAACP Centennial Convention; New York Post article about teacher salary hikes and other changes made by NYC Mayor Bloomberg and his chancellor, Joel Klein
- Officers, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  3/25/09 at 11:00AM. Agenda; United University Professions list of direct funding costs; news clipping re counterdemonstrators at Buffalo memorial service visited upon by three-person itinerant hate group; program for Local and Retiree Council Presidents Conference
- Officers, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  3/4/09 at 11:00AM. Agendas for Officers' and Cabinet meetings; letter from president of Buffalo Teachers Federation to NYSUT president Dick Ianuzzi complaining about unresponsive legal services, February 26
- Meeting with Dick, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  01/27/09 at 10AM. Memo re meeting
- Mini Officers Retreat, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  01/12/09 at 9AM in Fort Orange's Club. Facilitative memos
- Dinner with Officers, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  1/5/09. Poll questions with arguments for and against on school-related issues; memo
- Officers' Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  12/2/08 at 10AM. Agenda; memo from NYSUT executive director Pauline Kinsella to NYSUT president Dick Ianuzzi re collective bargaining issues in the current and anticipated economic climate, November 19; presentation to Board of Directors meeting, "Impact of the Economy on the State Budget"
- Officers' Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  11/19/08. Memo re cancellation
- Officers, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  11/04/08 at 9:30AM. Agenda; lists of Administrative Committee, NYSUT Advisory Committee, and Cabinet members; memo re Solidarity Grant recommendations
- Officers' Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  9/11/08 at 9:30AM. Agenda; program for ULTA (United Teachers of Los Angeles) Leadership Conference 2008; recommendations from Personnel Committee
- Officers' Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  05/07/08 at 11AM in Dick's Office. Agenda; Solidarity Fund grant applications
- NYSUT Policy Council-Maria Neira, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  10/7/09. Agenda; presentation bullet points, "Taking Charge of Our Professions"; document, Core Standards for Reading, Writing, and Speaking and Listening; draft document re college and career readiness standards for mathematics
- Policy Council, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  11/10/08 at 10:30AM in NYSUT HQ. Presentation points re 2008 Fiscal Crisis; State Education Department policy papers for decision, Submission of a Differentiated Accountability Model to the U.S. Department of Education, and Proposed Interim Growth Model for Title I Accountability; draft NYSUT High School Initiatives Task Force Strategies and Action Items for Improving Graduation Rates; attendance sheet for Policy Council meeting; list of Policy Council members for 2008-2011
- Policy Council, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  02/04/08 at 10AM in NYSUT HQ. Agenda; meeting attendance sheet; list of policy discussion groups; notes from November 8, 2007, meeting; draft NYSUT Briefing Bulletin re changes in tenure determination; Briefing Bulletins re 2008-09 Executive (governor's) Budget for Pre-K-12 and Higher Education; list of 2005-2008 Policy Council members; policy discussion paper re career and technical education; State Education Department discussion paper re Implementation of New Law on Teacher Tenure Determinations
- Policy Council, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  11/8/07 TBD. Facilitative memos
- Barry Kaufmann, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  Poughkeepsie Public School Teachers' Association president's resignation letter, coinciding with retirement as teacher
- NYSUT Policy Council Meeting, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  11/8/07 at 10-3PM in Conf. Rm. B&C. Agenda; NYSUT Policy Council Draft Discussion Paper, "Use of Peer Review in Making Tenure Determinations"; draft NYSUT Action Plan: Tenure Determinations; list of Policy Council members, 2005-08; draft resolution for Representative Assembly opposing merit pay for performance; draft resolution re Medicaid reimbursement for special education services
- Plattsburgh Regional Office Open House, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  9/25/07 at 3PM. Letter to NYSUT vice president Maria Neira from Plattsburgh regional staff director inviting her to open house for new facility; related memos
- Elmsford Regional Office Staff Meeting, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  10/27/06 at 10:00AM. Elmsford and NYC Regional Office staff meeting agenda; memo to regional staff directors re health benefits update; handwritten notes
- Research and Educational Services Dept. Staff Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  06/18/09 at 9AM in Conf. Room B&C. Agenda; final draft of speech, "States Will Lead the Way Toward Reform: National Governors Association"; NYSUT's Framework for Action on Teacher Quality; document re teacher quality and effectiveness
- Research and Educational Services Planning Session, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  5/5/09. List of schools in need of improvement under Title I, with cover press release from State Education Department, September 3, 2004; memo from NYSUT director of field operations to NYSUT officers re public employee strikes in New York (text of Taylor Law), September 19, 2005; summary of Division of Research and Educational Services Planning Conference, April 28-29, 2005; speech by Maria Neira at Representative Assembly, 2005
- Research and Educational Services Dept. Staff Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  9/9/08 at 9AM in Conf. Rm. B&C. List of small groups discussing "Charting Our Course"; discussion group work sheets; list of NYSUT's organizational frameworks; outline of staff meeting theme, "Staying Ahead of the Curve"
- Research and Educational Services Staff Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  6/18/08 at 9:00AM in Conf. Rm. B&C. Agenda; document, 2007-08 Review of Major Issues and Events; questions for table discussion on collaboration; memos
- Resarch & Ed. Svcs. Staff Meeting, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  06/29/06 at 9:00AM in NYSUT Auditorium. Agenda, including discussion item re assimilating NEA staff and review of unification rationale; highlights of June 29 meeting
- Research & Ed. Svcs., 2006 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  01/13/06 at 9:30PM in Chuck's Office. Agenda for managers' meeting; talking points for NYSUT president Dick Ianuzzi and vice president Maria Neira re Representative Assembly resolutions
- Research & Ed. Staff Meeting, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 72)